export const myQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital of Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte", b: "Jaffna", c: "Galle", d: "Kandy" },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Dhirham", b: "USD", c: "Yen", d: "Rupee" },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Longest river in Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Kalu River", b: "Mahaweli River", c: "Kelani River", d: "Maha River" },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the tallest mountain in Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Kirigalpotha", b: "Thotupola", c: "Pidurutalagala", d: "Adam's Peak" },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the highest waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Bambarakanda Falls", b: "Ravana Falls", c: "Diyaluma Falls", d: "Dunhinda Falls" },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "How many districts are there in Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "32", b: "50", c: "25", d: "15" },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main religion of Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Buddhism", b: "Hinduism", c: "Islam", d: "Christianity" },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "What animal appears on the flag of Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Cheetah", b: "Lion", c: "Elephant", d: "Dragon" },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "How many provinces are in Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "18", b: "15", c: "20", d: "9" },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Which ocean surrounds Sri Lanka?",
    answers: { a: "Atlantic Ocean", b: "Indian Ocean", c: "Pacific Ocean", d: "Arctic Ocean" },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  }
];